<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analysis on Co-purchases of pet supply items!</title><link>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Analysis on Co-purchases of pet supply items!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Community Analysis</title><link>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/data-description/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/data-description/</guid><description>As mentioned the full dataset did not make a fully connected graph, and instead many subnetworks appeared. The largest connected component consists of 21.627 products. This component helped understand what factors influence the purchasing patterns of pet supply customers. When computing community splits on the largest connected component, we can group the purchases, with items that they are often more bought with than others. This results in a split, that we can visualize, with each community of items bought together having different colors.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy</title><link>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/text-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/text-analysis/</guid><description> .large-image { width: 50%; /* Adjust the width as needed */ display: block; margin: auto; } .photo-grid { display: grid; grid-template-columns: repeat(3, 1fr); /* Adjust the number of columns as needed */ gap: 10px; /* Adjust the gap between images as needed */ margin-top: 20px; } .photo-grid img { width: 100%; height: auto; border-radius: 5px; /* Optional: adds a rounded border to images */ }</description></item><item><title>Item recommendation</title><link>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/network-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Frederik-N-H-Lundgren.github.io/frederik-n-h-lundgren.github.io/network-analysis/</guid><description>This page will be a good foundation for some items you might want to take a look at, when filling upi your basket on Amazon.
Dog are the most commenly described animal in the network, and this should come as no surprise. The beloved four legged pet, that sparks joy in everyone. If you want to give some of that spark back to your dog, we highly recommend you to take a look at these next few items.</description></item></channel></rss>